[Music]
for 15 years
we have kept the promises we have made
to our customers
as a result we have seen phenomenal
growth
leadership and recognition at icici
lombard
last year we kept our promises to the
tune of over 34 lakhs
in claims settlements and products
across automobile
health travel a home for business
across marine fire and property we
designed insurance to keep them
safe guarded we also covered speciality
solutions
like weather and crop insurance which
provided the much needed financial
protection to our farmers
and the rural economy to achieve all
this
we knew that we needed to be as close to
customers
as possible today with more than 5
thousand cashless garages
assisting automobile owners and three
thousand two hundred plus empaneled
hospitals
providing smooth healthcare services our
customers
know that they are in safe hands
our e-cashless module helps settle
claims in a lightning speed
while our customer service center is
always ready to address every customer
query
technology and innovation has been a
constant buzzword
at icici lombard whether it is through a
mobile app that enables quick and easy
policy transactions
or a product innovation like the
long-term two-wheeler insurance
or wellness advisor in health insurance
the unwavering focus
on our customers drives us to constantly
innovate our wealth of healthcare
information coupled with our in-house
capabilities
help us offer customized preventive
healthcare solutions
and personalized guidance to our
corporate customers
we have extended this proposition to the
general public
through health advisor an online
consumer-facing solution
that allows individuals to not only
locate the nearest hospital
but also compare services and treatment
costs offered by different hospitals
it also allows them to share their
hospital experiences
when required we also provide customized
telematics solutions
to our clients fleet owners so that they
can track vehicles
and reduce theft while controlling
losses
such value additions help us reinstill
the trust our customers have in us
we know we're in the business of
promises
and we also understand how important it
is to honor that promise when it matters
most
based on this principle our
organizational philosophy
of vishwas enables us to deliver on
these promises
time and again it is this strength
that makes us well poised not only for
the present
but also for the future
[Music]
you